EQ and DA run together, but of course we
cannot advise on the use of peeds on
this channel. Uh we don't promote nor
condone the use of peeds. Anything you
want to say about it? Uh Dave, for
entertainment purposes only. I mean they
are two very psychoactive
anabolic steroids and not in a good way.
So
equipoise gives a lot of men anxiety and
deca being a progesterine can also
really mess with a lot of men's mood as
well. So when you take those two things
and put them in as a cocktail, would you
have a fantastic anabolic response to
diet and training stimulus? Probably.
How is this going to end up for your
health and subjective state and your
overall endocrine system? Oh, you're
kind of really really rolling the dice
there. One of the challenges with deca
that a lot of guys don't realize is that
because the uh deca being short for
nandelone uh decaninoate that esester is
so long and the progesterine uh aspects
of it are so suppressive to the HBTA
axis that this can suppress your
production for like you know 6 to9
months after you stop taking it. So be
really careful if you're planning to use
nandelone decinoate for steroid cycles.
But I don't recommend people use
steroids at all. But if I was gun to my
head, if I had to do some kind of
steroid cycle, it would not be that one.
So I wouldn't